matt.meece.75@gmail.com

# **Objectives**

Seeking a full time position with a reputable employer that offers daily challenges and opportunities for professional growth and creativity, where my customer service and management skills are utilized.

# **Professional Summary**

I am a dedicated, driven individual, motivated to maintain customer satisfaction and contribute to company success. I have worked in the customer service industry my entire working life, and I get special satisfaction in exceeding expectations of both the customer and my employer.

#### **Core Qualifications**

- Customer service driven
- Energetic work attitude
- Detail oriented
- Self-starting
- Motivating management style

- Adaptive team player
- Proficient at multitasking
- Quick learner
- Cash handling
- Trustworthy and loyal

### **Experience**

#### **Assistant Store Manager**

March 2018 - March 2020

PRC, Inc. - Arlington, WA

Open the store, complying with and overseeing store security measures.

Created and implemented an employee handbook to boost productivity and moral of employees.

Assisted customers at all sales levels, offering a unique and diverse knowledge base.

Make deposits of store revenue to the secure safe, and responsible for filling the stores ATM machines.

Managed on average 14 active employees, including break schedules and supporting them in customer service needs.

#### **Relief Store Manager**

July 2016 - March 2018

Big 5 Sporting Goods - Burlington, WA

Make deposits of store revenue, and record financial information daily on general ledger.

Verify safe balance and contents daily.

Oversee all internal store departments, as well as employees in those departments.

Open and close the store, maintaining security protocol.

Versed in various management training courses, loss prevention, and sale compliance of regulated inventory.

## **Head Golf Technician**

November 2015 to April 2016

Dicks Sporting Goods - Marysville, WA

Oversaw shipping and receiving, product placement, and product ordering in the Golf Department.

Performed custom golf fittings and custom club orders, boosting sales.

 $\label{lem:managed} \mbox{Managed three employees in the Department, and handled all aspects of customer service.}$ 

Repaired golf clubs, using machinery and other tools.

# **Table Games Dual Rate Supervisor**

July 2010 to July 2015

Silver Reef Casino - Ferndale, WA

Educated customers on game rules and mathematical probabilities of various wagers.

Took and paid bets and retrieved cards.

Inspected cards and equipment to be used in games to verify proper functioning.

Maintained the integrity of table game operations by supervising table game dealers.

#### **Education**

Burlington Edison High School - High School Diploma - 1997

Skagit Valley Community College - 1997-1998